

# S.M. Ashadujjaman Tushar

An enthusiastic individual and recent graduate in Bachelor of Computer Science & Engineering . Extremely motivated to constantly develop my skills and grow professionally. I am confident in my ability to come up with interesting ideas for unforgettable marketing campaigns and team player with experience in leading, planning and executing within a deadline.

Present Address: 36/4 Rd No. 3, Shyamoli

Dhaka-1207, Bangladesh

**Contact:** +8801752322370

Email Address: ashadujjaman15-6862@diu.edu.bd

LinkedIn Profile: <a href="linkedin.com/in/ashadujjaman-tushar-459393186">linkedIn Profile: linkedin.com/in/ashadujjaman-tushar-459393186</a>

GitHub Profile: https://github.com/AshadujjamanTushar136

#### PERSONAL INFORMATION:

Name : S.M Ashadujjaman Tushar

Fathers Name : S.M Monirujjaman Nannu

Mothers Name : Most. Rashida Jaman

Nationality : Bangladeshi

Date of Birth : 17 March 1997

Marital Status : Unmarried

# **EDUCATION**

# **B.Sc.** in Computer Science & Engineering

**Daffodil International University** 

01/2016 - 01/2020, CGPA: 2.94

#### **Higher Secondary Certificate**

Patuakhali Government College

2014, GPA: 5

Background
- Science

## **Secondary School Certificate**

Patuakhali Government Jubilee High School 2012, GPA: 5

Background
- Science

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **Beginners Competitive Programming Trainer**

Daffodil International University

01/2017 - 12/2018

# **Affiliate Marketing**

Freelancer at Amazon Field

01/2017 - 12/2018

# **SKILLS**

MS Office: Expertise on PowerPoint, Excel and Word.

Have Little idea on Adobe Photoshop.

Basic Knowledge of HTML.

Team work, Time Management, Communication.

Problem Solving.

# **EXTRA-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES**

Executive Member, DIU Computer Programming Club (01/2017 - 12/2018)

Dhaka, Bangladesh

# LANGUAGES

Mother tongue and full working knowledge in Bengali.

Fluent in English.

# **HOBBIES AND INTERESTS**

Travelling, Football, Music, Singing

# **REFERENCES:**

**Professor Dr. Touhid** 

Bhuiyan

Position: Head

Organization Name: Daffodil International

University

Contact: +880 1847140016

Email: <a href="mailto:headcse@daffodilvarsity.edu.bd">headcse@daffodilvarsity.edu.bd</a>
Organization Address: 4/2, Daffodil

Tower, Sobhanbag, Mirpur Rd, Dhaka-1207

Mr. Md. Sadekur Rahman

**Position:** Assistant Professor **Organization Name:** Daffodil

International University **Contact:** 01676379698

Email:

sadekur.cse@daffodilvarsity.edu.bd Organization Address: 4/2, Daffodil

Tower, Sobhanbag, Mirpur Rd,

Dhaka1207